<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Warpspire</title>
 <link href="ubermind.github.io/feed" rel="self"/>
 <link href="ubermind.github.io/"/>
 <updated>2014-08-10T23:11:54+03:00</updated>
 <id>http://warpspire.com/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Kyle Neath</name>
   <email>kneath+warpspire@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Reinventing explanation</title>
   
     <link href="http://michaelnielsen.org/reinventing_explanation/index.html" />
   
   <updated>2014-08-04T00:00:00+03:00</updated>
   <id>http://warpspire.com/posts/rethinking-explanation</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Michael Nielsen on how to act upon knowledge :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;the core issue here isn&amp;rsquo;t just to learn a set of facts. It&amp;rsquo;s at least as  important to replace your old instinctive habits of thought with new habits of thought.
A conventional response to all this is to shrug our shoulders and say that some people are &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo;, meaning that they have strategies to convert knowledge of the facts into a change in their habits of thought, and that other people are &amp;ldquo;not so smart&amp;rdquo;, meaning that they don&amp;rsquo;t apply such strategies. I believe this is wrong, I believe we can and should improve our explanations to help people change their habits of thought.
We can do this by not just providing the facts, but by also directly cueing changes in people&amp;rsquo;s habits of thought. One simple idea for how to do this is to dramatize as vividly as possible the point at which an interruption in our thinking should occur. It&amp;rsquo;s that moment which we want people to recognize and act on, as it occurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Debuting my First iOS App?</title>
   
     <link href="ubermind.github.io//posts/My-First-iOS-App" />
   
   <updated>2013-12-02T00:00:00+03:00</updated>
   <id>http://warpspire.com/posts/My-First-iOS-App</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It was really a long journey to program this app given that I did it as a side project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in a nutshell PyDocs helps you read Python documentation on-the-go. you can browse and search the reference completely offline. It includes Docs for Python and common used 3rd party libraries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Python 2.7 , Python 3.3, Django , Flask , Numpy , Scipy ,Sickit-learn, Pandas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/images/iphone-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iphone snapshot&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/public/images/iphone-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iphone snapshot&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/public/images/iphone-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iphone snapshot&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find it on the app store &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/pydocs/id747985884?ls=1&amp;amp;mt=8&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>